Finding Aid for the Father James Harold Flye Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series 14 - Audio Tapes
  - Scientology or Dianetics; Nathan Hightower and Father Flye, 1960. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 118)
  - Scientology---Nathan Hightower, Nov. 1963. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 119)
  - Father Flye and Jackie, a homeless woman, Oct. 1963. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 120)
  - Father Flye and Jackie, Nov. 1966. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 121)
  - Father Flye and Jackie, Nov. 1967. 5 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 122)
  - Bob Laing, Martha Wittenbach, January 1959. 5 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 123)
  - Martha Wittenbach, April 1959. 5 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 124)
  - Chris and Todd, neighborhood children. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 125)
  - Letter from Tom Kenyon, July 1964; partial recording of The Inferno. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 126)
  - Phil Suttler, Verne Homsher, homeless men. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 127)
  - Side 1 Cleveland Amory (Box 63, Folder 128)
    - Side 2 Monica, indigent woman. 3 “ tape
  - Noel Parmentel. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 129)
  - Letter from the Rev. Thomas N. Lyons, early 1960s. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 130)
  - Don Yorks, April 1964. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 131)
  - Letter from Edward Simmen, Oct. 1964. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 132)
  - About Jack Smith. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 133)
  - Friday Group, Wichita; Mrs. Armstrong, 1961. 5 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 134)
  - Bob Temple and Father Flye, Oct. 1963. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 135)
  - Father Flye with Bart and Eleanor. 7 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 136)
  - Humorous lecture, March 1969. 3 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 137)
  - Father Flye and Stephen Henderson, March and Dec. 1969 and Oct. 1970. 7 “ tape (Box 63, Folder 138)
  - Father Flye and Benjamin Branch. 7 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 139)
  - Agnes Vadas playing Bach, Oct. 1979. Cassette (Box 64, Folder 140)
  - Father Flye and David Herwaldt. 7 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 141)
  - Father Flye and David Herwaldt. 7 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 142)
  - Father Flye and David Herwaldt. 7 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 143)
  - Father Flye and David Herwaldt. 7 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 144)
  - Father Flye and David Herwaldt. 7 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 145)
  - Father Flye, Jan. 1982. Cassette (Box 64, Folder 146)
  - Transcriptions of Soundscriber discs recorded by Father Flye, Wichita, 1956-1958. Cassettes (Box 64, Folder 147-153)
  - Discs 1-5, June 1956-April 1957 (Box 64, Folder 147)
  - Discs 6-9A, April 1957-July 1957 (Box 64, Folder 148)
  - Discs 9B-14B (first half), Aug. 1957-Oct. 1957 (Box 64, Folder 149)
  - Discs 14B (second half)-16 (partial), Oct. 1957-NewYear’s Day, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 150)
  - Discs 16-20 (partial), Jan. 1958-Spring 1960 (Box 64, Folder 151)
  - Disc 20 (completed). (Box 64, Folder 152)
  - Father Flye’s attempt to clarify Discs 4A&B and 5 A&B. (Box 64, Folder 153)
  - Father Flye and Nina Stroop, Spring 1960. 5 “ tape (Box 64, Folder 154)
  - Reception for Father Flye at the opening of his photography exhibit at St. Andrew’s, Oct. 10, 1980. Cassette (Box 64, Folder 155)